  C800000h-DF7FFFFh  Open Bus
  DFE0000h-DFFFFFFh  Open Bus
lines are open bus (containing the halfword address), so one can do:
usual open bus values though.
  D000000h  Open Bus? in retail version, Extra 16Mbyte MainRAM in debug version
  32MB (3)     1st 16MB            1st 16MB (mirror)   Open bus (or 2nd 16MB)
DSi retail consoles return 16bit open bus values instead of extra memory). RAM
